[{"answer": "Well, I think insecurities are feeding up on each other and although there's a sense that the problem is maybe fixable in economic sense but they may not be so fixable in a political sense.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "What's going on here?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Is that the sense you're getting?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "You know, I have -- I have a fairly different take.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "What do you make of him?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "He says the door isn't shut now on getting back on terms diplomatically with the U.S. Do you think that's a possibility?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, I guess two things.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "How have you managed to break down these barriers?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "And, you know, he employees other female staff now, he wants to get you driving a car in Saudi Arabia, which at the moment, women can't do, right?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, I really hope they do.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Do you think the barriers are coming down fast enough?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "In Saudi Arabia?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Everywhere I go.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Have you had lessons?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Everywhere I go.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "You drive every where else?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "In the desert I can.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "The only place you can't drive a car is in your country?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say frustrated.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "What are the things that really frustrate you about Saudi Arabia now that you'd love to change quickly as a young woman there?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "That's a tough question.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Can you appear like this on television in Saudi Arabia or would you have to be covered up?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I think the whole region is impatient.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Are you impatient for that?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "I think this generation is different than any other generation other than the fact that they're globalized and interconnected.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Is there a higher level of respect now?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "My husband?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "L-TAWEEL: Incredible.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "How did you find Bill Clinton?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "President Obama?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Do you think he's a force for good for women's rights in the world?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "I was with him the whole time.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "What would you like to say?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Has it been upsetting to you as his wife?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "That is true.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "You know that?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, I always -- honestly, I always feel like it's worth it.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Do you feel like, OK, it's worth it?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "ORGAN: My initial thinking really.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "I think evil might be a little bit of strong word, you know?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I'm a real mix.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Are you a good girl in real life?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "We had a late night and I did.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "I heard after the Emmy triumph on Sunday, you had a rather late night, Julianna?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "That's a very good question.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "So what does it mean to be a good wife?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Did you actually strike the poor man?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "I really think it would depend on the situation.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Would you stand by your man?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, actually when I was -- when we're very little -- my parents split when I was 1.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What were the memories you had of them splitting up and your life that you came I think to the United States with your mother and -- how much do you see of your father?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "(INAUDIBLE), darling.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Where did you go?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "You didn't?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "You didn't ever go to that nightclub in East Greenster (ph), did you?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I think people are going to find out soon enough on Sunday night on CBS.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "What does that mean exactly?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "That's what I'm hearing.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Allegations?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "I just don't think so.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Not a glimmer?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Absolutely brilliantly written.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "It's brilliantly written show, isn't it, with great characters?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "It's not that I don't like it.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Why don't you like the whole social network thing?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I enjoyed it as well.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "He took everybody down with it, didn't he?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "I think there's even worse dangers than that.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Isn't there a drunk Tweeting danger?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Never follow an ex girlfriend would be definitely top of the list, I think, don't you?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Actually, no.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Are you as pathetically unlucky in love in real life as you are on-screen?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I know, exactly.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "What's wrong with him?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Things are much better for me than Will Gardner, as far as his emotional life.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Real life, things are a lot happier?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "My girlfriend, Sophie, is not only comfortable with it.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Is she comfortable with these steamy love scenes that you're about to unfurl on the nation?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Your husband, you banned from watching?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I think you're holding something against her.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Alicia.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "I'm what?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Not at the same time, though.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "You, unless I'm wrong, were once quoted as saying \"I don't believe monogamy is feasible\" and I've been married to a woman and to a man?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "As man, I didn't feel my gender is particularly attuned to be monogamous.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "There's a glittering example sitting right next to you?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Like betraying them in friendship or betraying their trust.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "I think a big factor is when you have children and you're raising a family, staying together, I think the greatest gift Matthew and I gave our kids was staying together and working things out.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Christine?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "Do you understand how her character then would stand by her man?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "I think that must be awful.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "He hasn't got any TV show?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "Do you think he's inherently an evil person?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Wouldn't he, in the end, do anything for political gain?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Does he have a moral compass, though?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "What would you like to know, Piers?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "After you lost --", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Are you sure now you're on the right side of the fence?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Well, I think if -- I think, you know, there's such -- America's this country full of such hatred in terms of politics.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "What do you think of all these politicians, talking of politics, who on the Tea Party side of the Republicans, are coming out and saying same-sex marriage is disgusting and can't happen?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "Well, they have to come out of the hotel room, right?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "He is not going to waste that kind of money is my sense, not his character.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "Have you ever done that?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Have you all seen the first episode?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "See it Sunday.", "docId": "110922pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "Do you all get together for a \"Good Wife\" party?", "qSentId": 784}]